checking http://127.0.0.1:8000/news/stats ...
Stats Status: 200
Stats Response: {
  "total_articles": 1396,
  "new_today": 540,
  "status": "Live & Syncing"
}

checking http://127.0.0.1:8000/news/technology ...
Category Status: 200
Latest Technology Article: {
  "title": "Foundation stone for Kerala Institute of Organ Transplantation to be laid in Kozhikode on February 7",
  "content": "Chief Minister Pinarayi Vijayan will lay the foundation stone for the Kerala Institute of Organ Transplantation at Chevayur, Kozhikode, on Saturday (February 7, 2026).\n\nHealth Minister Veena George will preside over the function. Ministers P.A. Mohamed Riyas and A.K. Saseendran will also be present on the occasion.\n\nThe Institute, being established at a cost of \u20b9643.88 crore through KIIFB funding, will be a fully autonomous centre of excellence in the public sector, functioning as a single umbrella under which all organ transplant-related activities in the State \u2013 including organ donation initiatives, transplant surgeries, post-transplant rehabilitation as well as training and research activities \u2013 will take place.\n\nComprehensive activities related to organ transplantation, right from the management of organ failure till post-transplant follow-up care, academic activities, research in organ, tissue and cell transplantation will be the responsibility of the Institute.\n\n350-bed facility\n\nThe facility will come up in three blocks with eight floors each. It will house 350 beds, including intensive care units, high dependency units, and dialysis facilities.\n\nThe Institute will also include a dedicated transplant research centre and a centre for cell and tissue engineering. In the first phase, 14 specialty departments and divisions will be established. A total of 31 academic courses have been planned, many of which will be the first of their kind in the country, an official statement here said.\n\nThe Institute will begin functioning at Kozhikode Medical College and move to its own facility later. The State government has sanctioned 60 posts for the Institute in the first phase",
  "summary": "Chief Minister Pinarayi Vijayan will lay the foundation stone for the Kerala Institute of Organ Transplantation at Chevayur, Kozhikode, on Saturday (February 7, 2026).\n\nHealth Minister Veena George will preside over the function. Ministers P.A. Moham...",
  "source": "The Hindu",
  "url": "https://www.thehindu.com/news/national/kerala/foundation-stone-for-kerala-institute-of-organ-transplantation-to-be-laid-in-kozhikode-on-february-7/article70599933.ece",
  "image_url": "https://www.thehindu.com/theme/images/og-image.png",
  "author": "Authors",
  "publish_date": "2026-02-06T11:51:42",
  "category": "Technology",
  "region": null,
  "tags": null,
  "sentiment_score": 0.0,
  "bias_label": null,
  "quality_score": 80.0,
  "readability_score": 0.0,
  "feed_score": 80.0,
  "is_featured": false,
  "is_clickbait": false,
  "read_time_minutes": 1,
  "view_count": 0,
  "id": 1110,
  "slug": null,
  "created_at": "2026-02-06T14:06:39",
  "updated_at": null
}
